Digital Marketing Analyst ROBERT SMITH

Phone: (123) 456 78 99 Email: info@qwikresume.com Website: www.qwikresume.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/qwikresume Address: 1737 Marshville Road,

Alabama.

Objective

As a public relations and marketing professional with significant experience of 2 years as a Digital Marketing Analyst in SEO enhanced copywriting and content management, I've become an expert in a variety of fields, including social media management and networking, blogging, and technical writing.

Skills

Marketing, Public Relations, Content Management, Marketing, Writing, Editing, Journalism, Branding, Content Development, Media Training, Media Relations, Media Tracking, Social Networking, Campaign Management, Development, And Social Media Management.

Work Experience

Digital Marketing Analyst

Opportunity Max - 2015 - 2017

- Educate clients on best local search practices to improve upon existing SEO strategies.
- Research keyword trends via google analytics, google webmaster tools and google trends.
- Provide clients with strategic recommendations to improve organic search performance.
- Develop and present reporting presentations, showcasing program results and recommendations based on past performance and strategy.
- Perform research based on trending topics and keywords related to client goals and events.
- Write, edit, and manage both internal blogs and client blogs using current SEO standards and best practices.
- Research trending keywords and topics to develop weekly and monthly content calendars and editorial guides.

Director- Digital Marketing

Girlsaskguys.com - 2015 - 2015

- Oversee all areas of internal and external content development and management.
- Generate SEO enhanced daily content to be featured and promoted on the site.
- Manage the site's user content creation feature to ensure quality content is being shared and created.
- Measure social media analytics to track engagement, influence, and presence.
- Execute and manage unique strategies for Facebook, Pinterest, Twitter, and google+.
- Develop social media procedures and practices for implementation across all three sites.
- Manage multiple social campaigns, both paid and organic, to measure conversions.

Education

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE in Public Relations & Creative Writing - 2005 to 2009(University Of Central Missouri - Warrensburg, MO)